<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About Me on stella koh</title>
    <link>http://skokoh.github.io/categories/about-me/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in About Me on stella koh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="/categories/about-me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>stella koh</title>
      <link>http://skokoh.github.io/post/2017/04/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 19:17:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://skokoh.github.io/post/2017/04/intro/</guid>
      <description>Eunjeong (Stella) Koh 

My name is Eunjeong Ko (고은정). I am a Ph.D. Candidate at UC San Diego, working on machine learning, affective computing, and interactive multimedia system, advised by Prof. Shlomo Dubnov. During my Ph.D., I have been very fortunate to intern at Smule (San Francisco CA), Gracenote (Emeryville CA), Qualcomm (San Diego CA), and Adobe research (Seattle WA). Before my Ph.D. study, I was a software engineer at Samsung Electronics, working on an automatic text reply system on Samsung smartwatch and question-answering system on Samsung smart TV, advised by Dr. Jihie Kim. I got my master’s degree from Seoul National University, working on music information retrieval with Prof. Kyogu Lee, and my bachelor’s degree from Ewha Womans University, working on Human-Computer Interaction research with Prof. Yanghee Nam. 


cv
Research Interests 
Music Information Retrieval, Machine Learning for Audio/Music Applications, Sound Design, Auditory Perception &amp;amp; Cognition 
Education 
 Sep 2016 – Ph.D. Student at Music, UC San Diego, CA  2012 – 2014. M.S. Engineering at Music &amp;amp; Audio Research Group, Seoul National University, South Korea (advisor: Kyogu Lee)  2008 – 2012. B.S. Computer Science and Engineering at Ewha Womans University, South Korea   Experiences</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
